

## SKILLS

- Html, Css, Js, Bootstrap
- Php, Codeigniter
- MySQL
- · React, Angular
- Node js, Mongo Db
- · Git & Git hub

# **PERSONAL STRENGTHS**

- Creativity
- · Adaptability
- Communication
- · Time Management
- Teamwork

# **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Experienced PHP developer with 2+ years in Codelgniter, MySQL, HTML, CSS, and jQuery. Proficient in user-friendly web app creation, strong in database management. Recently worked with Angular, Node.js, MongoDB, and completed React/MERN course. staying up-to-date in development. Valuable asset to any team.

#### CONTACT



8870694783



balusiva2312@gmail.com



in https://www.linkedin.com/in/si vakumar-b-6863891b1

🡤 211/16, KR Nagar, Aranthangi 614616, Pudukkottai (DT).

# SIVAKUMAR B

### FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

To become a successful professional in a highly competitive technological world where performance is rewarded with new challenging responsibilities and to serve a reputed growth-oriented industry in the field of design, development, and maintenance

## **EDUCATION**

2021 - 2023

Alagappa University, Distance Education

Master of Computer Applications

2017 - 2020

Alagappa Government Arts College

**Bachelor of Computer Applications** 

2016 - 2017

**Vestley Matric Higher Secondary** School

**HSC** 82.5%

2014 - 2015

**Annai Higher Secondary School** 

SSI C 88%

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

2020 - 2022

#### Web Developer

AGM Technical Solutions Co WLL

- · Proficient in PHP, MySQL, and Codelgniter for web application development.
- · Currently utilizing Angular, Node.js, and MongoDB to create modern, scalable web solutions.
- · Collaborating within cross-functional teams to deploy and optimize web applications.
- · Committed to staying updated on emerging web development trends.
- · Possessing a versatile skill set encompassing a wide range of technologies.

#### **PHP Developer**

Lakshminivaasam, Chennai

- Experience developing PHP / MySQL / JavaScript websites
- Good understanding of databases, specifically MySQL
- Comfortable with contributing to complex technical discussions
- Experience developing PHP And MySQL Dynamic website